

Atsuko Tominaga

Vechtdal 48 6718NK Ede

 \Box +31625427606

me@atsukotominaga.com

in atsukotominaga

Skills

Organisational skills	9+ yrs.
Communication/ Collaboration	9+ yrs.
Research	5+ yrs.
Data management Data analysis	5+ yrs.
Microsoft Office	9+ yrs.

Languages

Japanese	Native
English	C1
Dutch	B1

Profile

I am originally from Japan and moved to Europe in 2016. I have more than 5 years of research experience in psychology and previously worked as a coordinator in a Japanese research institute and a Japanese startup company in the Netherlands. I am looking for a job where I can use my cultural background and international experience to help people connect in a multicultural environment.

Experience

Administrative Coordinator

04/2023 - 06/2023

TYPICA (Direct Trade Specialty Coffee Platform), Netherlands

I facilitated communication between the Japanese and Dutch offices, supported Japanese employee immigration and managed various administrative tasks in a Japanese startup company.

Scientific Coordinator

04/2016 - 08/2016

Kokoro Research Center, Kyoto University, Japan

I mainly performed secretarial work for the institution's director (managing the director's schedules, preparing for meetings etc.). I also organised conferences and scientific events, arranged travel for researchers, and managed research funds.

Assistant Manager

07/2014 - 03/2016

Keibunsha Ichijoji Bookstore, Japan

I provided customer service in-store and online, implemented stock management system, updated the website with new content (products and marketing blogs) and organised events such as workshops at an independent local bookstore.

Scientific Coordinator

06/2013 - 06/2014

Kokoro Research Center, Kyoto University, Japan

Same as above.

Education

Ph.D. Cognitive Science

09/2017 - 06/2023

Central European University, Austria

I conducted literature reviews to identify key problems and solutions, coordinated tasks and timelines, managed and analysed human behavioural data and presented research findings at internal meetings and international conferences.

M.Res. (Distinction) Psychology

10/2016 - 01/2018

University of York, United Kingdom

I studied experimental design/methods, statistics, basic programming (R and python) and social psychology.

B.Ed. Education (Psychology)

04/2009 - 03/2013

Kyoto University, Japan

I majored in cognitive psychology and studied surrounding areas (neuroscience, clinical psychology, educational psychology etc.)